Guide to the Max Wilk Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- February 2009 Acquisition, 1735-2007; 37; 20.02; (19 boxes) + 1 record album storage
  - Audio recordings
    - Audiocassettes, 1939-2002
      - "Box #6: Rare Music, (Musical Performers), Show Tunes, Radio and NPR", 1939-2000
        - "David Raksin", undated; 1 (Box 116, Item barcode 39002104610994)
          Includes photograph of Raksin which reads: David Raskin at 96 - taken in 1998 by Stephen Paley; "David Raskin: Hollywood Movie Music and the Price of Excellence"
    - Compact disc, 2005
      - Caught in the Act: Songs from the Great Days of Vaudeville, 2005; 1 compact disc (Box 117)
    - Record albums, 1949-1973
      - Yale Concert: Duke Ellington and His Orchestra, Fantasy Records, 1973; 1 12" record album (Box 118 (Record album storage))
      - By Jupiter, Decca recording, undated; 2 10" record albums (Box 118 (Record album storage))
      - Mary Martin Sings For You, Columbia Records, 1949; 1 10" record album (Box 118 (Record album storage))
  - Oversize
    - And Miss Carter Wore Pink: Scenes From An Edwardian Childhood, by Helen Bradley, 1971 (Box 119 (Oversize))
    - Hambleton, T. Edward, photograph, 2005 (Box 119 (Oversize))
    - Wilk, Barbara - memorial, 2007 (Box 119 (Oversize))
    - Stewart, Donald Ogden - plastic framed photograph, 1979 (Box 120 (Oversize))
    - Academy of Television Arts & Science tote bag, undated (Box 121 (Oversize))
- August 2011 Acquisition, 1930-2010; 38; 11.71; (16 boxes)
  Writings by Wilk and others; correspondence; notes; personal records; printed material; videocassettes and electronic files.
  Box 135 (audiovisual material): Restricted fragile. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
  - Nussbaum, Adam, 1977-1996 (Box 122)
  - "Mr. Williams and Miss Wood", undated (Box 122)
  - "Sweet Bye and Bye", undated (Box 122)
  - Frickert, Maude, notes, 2001, undated; 2 (Box 122)
  - "The Gospel According to Bobby Waters", undated; 2 (Box 122)
  - "Get Out and Get Under", undated; 2 (Box 122)
  - "Bypass", 1990 (Box 122)
  - Berlin bio, (Gottlieb), 1988 (Box 122)
  - "Indian Giver", undated (Box 122)
  - "Many Happy Returns", 1982 (Box 122)
  - Untitled typescript, undated (Box 122)
  - "My Masterpiece", undated (Box 122)
  - Financial records re: Hershey, 1982-1997 (Box 122)
  - Correspondence and printed material, 1993-2001 (Box 122)
  - Max Wilk, sketches, 1979 (Box 122)
  - "These are the Jokes", 1990 December (Box 122)
  - "A note on which the type of the type in which this work was originally composed", 1996 March (Box 122)
  - "Summer Camp O'Neil", undated (Box 122)
  - "Have a Heart", 1991-1995 (Box 122)
  - "Queen Lear", 2000 (Box 122)
  - "Long Term Memories: Listening to Al Hirschfeld", undated (Box 122)
  - "The Great Andy Warhol Caper", 2006; 2 (Box 122)
  - "I've Been in Ireland All Week, Now Let's Go to Liverpool!", undated (Box 122)
  - "Nobody's Heart", 2005 (Box 122)
  - Perelman manuscript "Malice in Wonderland," "Harburg," typescripts and correspondence, 1959, 1981 (Box 122)
  - "A Celebration of the Life of Ruth Nathan", 2005 (Box 122)
  - "Hanging Around With Talent," typescript, 2006, undated (Box 122)
  - "A Bad Case of February", 1960 (Box 123)
  - Reeves, Rosser, 1960-1982; 4 (Box 123)
  - "Slowly I Turn", undated (Box 123)
  - "Help", undated (Box 123)
  - "Mr. Williams and Miss Woods," revised pages, 1994 February (Box 123)
  - Holtz, Lou, undated (Box 123)
  - Typescripts, and photographic printouts, undated (Box 123)
  - Extras, (additional copies) Genius Pieces, 1984, undated (Box 123)
  - Wood, Audrey, book contracts, 1973-1985 (Box 123)
  - "American Treasure Hunt," book contract, 1985 March 7 (Box 123)
  - "Candy Is Dandy", 1993-1994; 2 (Box 123)
  - "Courtroom Blues", 2001 June 31 (Box 123)
  - "Mad Dogs and Englishmen," typescript, printed material, 2003, undated (Box 123)
  - "Jack Benny in London," typescript, 2003, undated (Box 123)
  - "Schmucks", 2004 (Box 123)
  - "A Ton of Bricks", 1962, undated; 2 (Box 123)
  - "A Bad Case of February", 1960-1961, undated; 4 (Box 124)
  - "A Ton of Bricks", 1963; 2 (Box 124)
  - "Down the Rabbit Hole," outline, 1994 (Box 124)
  - "Candy Is Dandy", 1993 (Box 124)
  - "Mean Creek", undated (Box 124)
  - "Furia", undated (Box 124)
  - Medical records, 2006; 2 (Box 124)
  - Extras, talent pieces, 2005, undated (Box 124)
  - Short pieces, undated (Box 124)
  - "Mr. Williams and Miss Wood", 2002-2003, undated; 2 (Box 124)
  - "Schmucks with Underwood", 2004-2005 (Box 124)
  - "Nobody's Hart", undated (Box 124)
  - "How I Spent My Summer Vacation", 1978- 2006 (Box 124)
  - Miscellaneous, 1946-2006; 4 (Box 124)
  - "Gifts to Yale", 1997-2006 (Box 125)
  - "Overture and Finale", undated (Box 125)
  - Deli book, 1990-1998 (Box 125)
  - Notes for Livingston and Evans narration, 2003 June (Box 125)
  - Letters, typescript, 2 clippings (Jake Wilk's obituary), 1956-1957 (Box 125)
  - "Down the Rabbit Hole", 1996 October (Box 125)
  - "Westward, Mr. Ho", 1991 July (Box 125)
  - "Jazz", 2004 (Box 125)
  - "Jack Benny in London," "Raise the Bridge," "Supper with Laurel and Hardy", undated (Box 125)
  - Ransom Library (Texas), 1991-1990 (Box 125)
  - "A Dirty Mind Never Sleeps", undated (Box 125)
  - "Reach for the Sky", undated (Box 125)
  - Untitled typescripts, undated; 2 (Box 125)
  - "Slowly I Turn", 1967 August (Box 125)
  - "Mr. Williams and Miss Wood", 1989, undated; 2 (Box 125)
  - Notes, undated (Box 125)
  - Letter to Max Wilk from Rice Pilafi, undated (Box 125)
  - "On Your Way", undated (Box 125)
  - "New York City Story", 1969 (Box 125)
  - Segment Title: "The Dream", undated (Box 125)
  - "Staff Hippy", undated (Box 125)
  - "The Cowboys", 1969, undated; 2 (Box 125)
  - "The Kowboys", undated (Box 125)
  - More AW odds and ends, 1950-1981 (Box 126)
  - "Mr. Williams and Miss Wood", 1981-1982, undated; 3 (Box 126)
  - "Herbie B.", 2000, undated (Box 126)
  - "Malice in Wonderland" (photocopy), undated (Box 126)
  - These are the Jokes", 1987 October (Box 126)
  - "Raggedy Ann.. .", 1991-1992 (Box 126)
  - Perelman, S. J., 1981-1982 (Box 126)
  - Groucho's speech about writers, 1957 (Box 126)
  - "Cloud Seven" copyright, 1985 June (Box 126)
  - "A Bad Case of February", 1960 (Box 126)
  - "Yellow Submarine", 1988 (Box 126)
  - "The Millikans", 1955, undated (Box 126)
  - "Fairy Story", 1970 October (Box 126)
  - "Ombudsman", 1969 (Box 126)
  - "A Dirty Mind Never Sleeps" (photocopy), 1970, undated; 2 (Box 126)
  - "American Music", 1966-1975; 2 (Box 126)
  - "The Brain Drain", 1965, undated (Box 126)
  - "The Great Long Island Bonanza", 1958 (Box 126)
  - "Ghost of a Rider", 1956 (Box 126)
  - "Everybody Loves a Loser", undated (Box 126)
  - Ford/Hayward, 1969 February (Box 126)
  - "The Kowboys", 1969, undated; 2 (Box 126)
  - "The Wreck of the Old '97", 1956 (Box 126)
  - "Mad Dogs and Englishmen", 2002, undated (Box 126)
  - Untitled typescript, undated (Box 126)
  - "Candy Is Dandy", 2003, undated; 2 (Box 127)
  - "These are the Jokes" (photocopy), undated (Box 127)
  - Cockenoe Uprising story, 1969 (Box 127)
  - "In Strangest America", 1956 (Box 127)
  - "A Vision: Revised", 1957 January (Box 127)
  - "American Airlines Presentation", 1967 October 27 (Box 127)
  - "A Cry for Help", undated (Box 127)
  - "The Cutting Edge", 1955 (Box 127)
  - "Five Hundred Times", 1956, 1961 (Box 127)
  - "How To Build a Chair", undated (Box 127)
  - "The Kowboys", 1969; 2 (Box 127)
  - And Did You Once See Sidney Plain? (photocopy), undated (Box 127)
  - Notes, undated (Box 127)
  - "Try This On Your Piano", undated (Box 127)
  - "Mr. Williams and Miss Wood" (photocopy), undated (Box 127)
  - "Hail Caesar", 1996 (Box 127)
  - Kaye, Jim, 1996 December (Box 127)
  - Correspondence, invoices, bills and receipts, 1977-1998 (Box 127)
  - Bills, copyright forms and other papers, 1932-1997 (Box 127)
  - "Don't Raise the Bridge", 1967 (Box 127)
  - "Brain Drain," clippings, 1967 (Box 127)
  - "Rex Harrison and Rachel Roberts: Weekend In Paris" (photpcopy), undated (Box 127)
  - "The Bug", undated (Box 127)
  - "The Island That Lived For a Day", 1968 (Box 127)
  - Copies: Warner Brothers photos; reviews "Schmucks", 2004 (Box 127)
  - Statistics (edited), undated (Box 127)
  - Correspondence from expandable file
    Contents removed from expandable file for preservation purposes.
    - "Agents", 1966 (Box 127)
    - "House Real Estate", 1966 (Box 127)
    - "X-Y-Z", 1967 (Box 127)
  - Notebook, 2010, undated (Box 127)
  - Printed material, 2000, 2003 (Box 127)
  - Kantor, Michael, 1995-2001 (Box 127)
  - "Sound of Music", 1999 (Box 127)
  - Max Wilk crossword puzzle, 2003, undated (Box 127)
  - Untitled typescripts, undated; 2 (Box 127)
  - Unsorted papers, 2003-2007; 2 (Box 127)
  - Baumeister, 1992 (Box 128)
  - Fidelity, 1981-1982 (Box 128)
  - ASCAP license, 2006-2008 (Box 128)
  - Addresses, undated (Box 128)
  - SBLI, 1991-2003 (Box 128)
  - Hallmark (Ray Evans), 2005, undated (Box 128)
  - Clearances "Song;" drawings (Schmucks), 1972-2003; 2 (Box 128)
  - Sherriff, R. C., and Sidney Buchman with notes, 1972-1973 (Box 128)
  - Selz, Peter, 1963-2007; 2 (Box 128)
  - Gifts 2000, 1998-2004 (Box 128)
  - "Where Were the Beatles?", undated; 2 (Box 128)
  - "These Are the Jokes", 1987 (Box 128)
  - Novel/book, 1984-1985 (Box 128)
  - Lewis, Al, manuscript, 1973-1979 (Box 128)
  - "The Brass Section," "Summer Camp O'Neil", undated (Box 128)
  - "The Tunnel of Love", undated (Box 128)
  - "Backstage With Talen", undated (Box 128)
  - Unproduced material, 1948 January 1 (Box 128)
  - Jule/Andy Warhol, undated (Box 128)
  - "The Rotten Book", 2003, undated (Box 128)
  - "Miss Rhinestone", 2003, undated (Box 128)
  - Rogers, Richard, 2001-2002 (Box 128)
  - "Storm Warning Redux" (photocopy), undated (Box 128)
  - The Tunnel of Love", undated (Box 129)
  - "WowoweeWeewo!" (photocopy), undated (Box 129)
  - "Tom and Marilyn" 2 copies, 1996 (Box 129)
  - Name droppings, undated (Box 129)
  - Short takes: "Nobody Loves a Producer", undated (Box 129)
  - "Four Musketeers Out of Town", 1998, undated; 2 (Box 129)
  - Various O'Neil people over the years, 1998-2004 (Box 129)
  - "Candy Is Dandy", 1993-1994; 4 (Box 129)
  - "Mad Dogs and Englishmen", 2006 March (Box 129)
  - "Don't Raise the Bridge", 1967 (Box 129)
  - "Getting Even", undated (Box 129)
  - "A Ton of Bricks", undated (Box 129)
  - "These are the Jokes", 1987; 2 (Box 129)
  - "Down the Rabbit Hole", 1996 (Box 129)
  - Untitled typescripts, undated; 3 (Box 129)
  - "Open the Door Barney", 1973-2008 (Box 130)
  - Copies of autographed letters et al., 1972-1973 (Box 130)
  - Ella Winter, Viertel, Don Stewart, 1971-1972 (Box 130)
  - Clippings, pamphlets, 1971-2005; 3 (Box 130)
  - Contracts, business, etc..., 1974-1976 (Box 130)
  - Unidentified typescript, notepad, printed material, 1992, undated (Box 130)
  - Musical Jubilee, 1970-1992 (Box 130)
  - Bank checks and deposit slips, 1972-1974 (Box 130)
  - Memory Lane, 1974-1978 (Box 130)
  - Critiques, 1983-1986 (Box 130)
  - Comedians, 1972-1988 (Box 130)
  - "Make 'Em Laugh", 2004; 2 (Box 130)
  - "Candy Is Dandy", 1993 (Box 130)
  - CV, clippings, 1998, 2005 (Box 130)
  - Film, The Secret Storm, 1971-2005 (Box 130)
  - Warhol (review), untitled typescripts, 2005, undated (Box 130)
  - "Feather in Your Cap" and untitled typescripts, 1962, undated (Box 130)
  - "Grant Avenue", undated (Box 130)
  - "Sidney Buchman, Harry Cohn's Fair Haired boy", 1983, January (Box 130)
  - "Mr. B", undated (Box 130)
  - Scrapbook cover, undated (Box 130)
  - "Test Pattern", undated (Box 130)
  - "Try This On Your Piano" (photocopy), undated (Box 130)
  - "Redskin Redskin Why Are You Blue?", undated (Box 130)
  - Miscellaneous, 1981-2003; 3 (Box 130)
  - Writers Guild of America Manual, 1985-1988; 2 (Box 131)
  - "Every Day's a Matinee", undated; 2 (Box 131)
  - "Voices of the 20th Century", 2000 October (Box 131)
  - "Open the Door Barney" (photocopy), undated (Box 131)
  - "Mad Dogs and Englishmen", 2002 (Box 131)
  - Songwriters (notes) "They're Playing Our Song" reviews, etc.., 1973-1997 (Box 131)
  - Christie's, 1987-1988 (Box 131)
  - "The Exchange", 2006-2007; 2 (Box 131)
  - "Waves of Laughter" a presentation, circa 1976 (Box 131)
  - Various pieces, 1983, undated (Box 131)
  - "Backstage With Talent", undated (Box 131)
  - 2 drawings by A. J. Copeland, undated (Box 131)
  - Letters to me, some important, 1970-2005 (Box 131)
  - "They're Playing Our Song", 1971 (Box 131)
  - "The Midnight Frolics", 1994 (Box 131)
  - "Redskin Redskin Why Are You Blue?", undated (Box 131)
  - "Crash", 2004 (Box 131)
  - Teaching Is Listening, 1972 (Box 131)
  - "Rotten Book" dead pages, first draft and rewrite, undated (Box 131)
  - For proposals, undated (Box 131)
  - "Candy Is Dandy", 1993 (Box 131)
  - Clipping, 1977 August 4 (Box 131)
  - COMC, Inc. shares, 2006 March (Box 131)
  - Eugene O'Neil Theatre, stage production program, 2006 March (Box 131)
  - "Al", 1987-2000 (Box 131)
  - Financial records, 1990-1998 (Box 131)
  - "Schmucks," draft, undated (Box 131)
  - T-Ring Publishers photograph and clipping, 1993, undated (Box 131)
  - "Jazz 1995", 1995-1999 (Box 131)
  - Papers related to Wilk's books, 1993-2008 (Box 131)
  - "Don't Tread On Me", 1975, undated (Box 131)
  - "Teardown", 2004 (Box 132)
  - "Lane", 2006 November 6 (Box 132)
  - "There are Times When Honesty Is Not the Best Policy," "Never Argue With a Hit," and Obituaries, 1992-1998, undated (Box 132)
  - "The Wit and Wisdom of the 20th Century", 1992-1998, undated (Box 132)
  - "Leicester Square", undated (Box 132)
  - "Wowoweeweeoh!" (photocopy), undated (Box 132)
  - Livingston, Jay and Ray Evans, 1996, undated; 3 (Box 132)
  - "Grant Avenue", 1987 November (Box 132)
  - "Type A", 1991 (Box 132)
  - "Feather In Your Cap", undated (Box 132)
  - Notes, undated (Box 132)
  - London book, miscellaneous, 1960-1964, 1997 (Box 132)
  - Ephemera (NB) !, 1978-2007, undated; 2 (Box 132)
  - "Doing the Next-To-Closing Mambo," (Jack Warner), undated (Box 132)
  - "You Always Need a Plumber", undated (Box 132)
  - "Who Said You Did", undated (Box 132)
  - "They're Playing Our Song", 2005, undated (Box 132)
  - Hecht, Ben, undated (Box 132)
  - "Madcap Mabel Normand," clippings, 1930 (Box 132)
  - Correspondence re: Wilk's books and Professor Furia, 1999, undated; 2 (Box 132)
  - Very rare stuff, 1955-2005 (Box 132)
  - English stuff circa 1964, undated (Box 132)
  - "Dear Me. Trenholme," short story, 1955 (Box 132)
  - "Labor of Love", 1961 (Box 132)
  - Eugene O'Neil Theatre, printed material, 1987-2002 (Box 132)
  - "Bypass", 1990; 2 (Box 132)
  - "Small Pieces of a Very Large Mosaic", 1978 (Box 132)
  - "Don and Ella", 1996 (Box 132)
  - Star list, 1987 (Box 133)
  - Notes, 2006-2008 (Box 133)
  - Writers Guild of America West, invoice, 2008 (Box 133)
  - Financial records, 2004 (Box 133)
  - Account ledger, 2004 (Box 133)
  - "The Relatives," "Belle's Boy," "Maxismo," "Maple Sugar on Navajo Fry Bread", 1976, undated (Box 133)
  - Untitled typescripts, undated; 4 (Box 133)
  - Miscellaneous, 1956-2003; 4 (Box 133)
  - Miscellaneous, 1965-2006; 9 (Box 134)
  - Videocassettes, 2004
    - Broadway: The American Musical, episodes 1-3, 2004 September 7; YCALMSS828_0001; 1; 00:58:21 (Box 135, Item barcode 39002102370245)
      Episode One: Give My Regards to Broadway (1893-1927)
      Episode Two: Syncopated City (1919-1933)
      Episode Three: I Got Plenty O' Nuttin' (1930-1942)
    - Broadway: The American Musical, Episode 1 "Give My Regards to Broadway" letterbox, 2004 September 7; YCALMSS828_0002; 1; 00:59:41 (Box 135, Item barcode 39002102370252)
  - Computer media
    - Mr. Williams & Miss Wood By Max Wilk Directed By Michael Holmes STARRING Diana Angelina & Richard Scofield Recorded Live at The Chandler Studio on 9/2/2002, 2011-ycal-46172-0001; 1 (Box 136)
    - YIP HARBURG DISC 1, 2011-ycal-46172-0002; 1 (Box 136)
      Yip Harburg at the Taper Forum with Paula Kelly, February 5, 1973
    - JOLSON WITH BARRY GRAY OCT. 27, 1946 for MAX WILK, 2011-ycal-46172-0003; 1 (Box 136)
      Inscribed to Max Wilk by Michael Feinstein.
  - "Help! Help! Help!" original illustrations, undated; 4 (Box 137 (Oversize))
  - "Big White Fog," Federal Theatre window poster, undated (Box 137 (Oversize))
  - "Horse Eats Hat," Federal Theatre window poster, undated (Box 137 (Oversize))
  - Newspaper clippings (photocopies), undated (Box 137 (Oversize))
- October 2016 Acquisition, 1930s-2000s; 39; 15.67; (15 boxes)
  Boxes 148-149 (audiovisual material): Restricted fragile. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
  - Writers Guild of America newsletter, 1969-1971 (Box 140)
  - Birthday poem, undated (Box 140)
  - Jewelry, undated (Box 140)
  - Collectible cars, circa 1970s; (3 folders) (Box 140)
  - Notebook, 1960s-1970s (Box 140)
  - Marilyn Monroe paperback, 1955- (Box 140)
  - Photograph, circa 1930s (Box 140)
    Photograph is of Jacob Wilk, Jack Warner, Albert Einstein, Elsa Einstein, Darryl Zanuck, Henry Blanke, Colonel Nathan Levinson, Hal Wallis and unkowns.
  - Calder booklet, Museum of Modern Art, 1943- (Box 140)
  - Ephemera, undated, 1960s (Box 140)
    Images from theater production and a Jean Dubuffet booklet.
  - Class photograph, 1941- (Box 140)
  - New York Times, Moon landing, 1969-07-21- (Box 140)
  - Correspondence, undated (Box 140)
  - Photographs and related materials, circa 1920s-1990s (Box 140)
  - Datebook, 1945 (Box 140)
  - Artwork, "Stress, One Size Fits All", undated (Box 140)
  - Newspaper clippings, circa 1970s (Box 140)
  - Receipts and other documents, 1980s-2000s (Box 140)
  - Book contracts and related correspondence, 1970s-1980s (Box 141)
  - Yale radio plays, 1939- (Box 141)
  - Oklahoma! research materials, undated (Box 141)
  - Harry Warren interview transcript and notes, circa 1972 (Box 141)
  - School and college publications, 1968- (Box 141)
  - Sheet music, circa 1930s-1950s; (3 folders) (Box 141)
  - Matzo Ball Soup, laminated drawing, undated (Box 141)
  - Photographs, Circa 1930s-1970s (Box 141)
  - Correspondence, Cambanellis to Wilk, 1969- (Box 141)
  - Writings, circa 1965 (Box 141)
    Titled included are "Disaster Under the Elms", and "1920: This was the Year that Was".
  - Contract materials from "Kissinger Noodles", 1986- (Box 141)
  - Contract agreements and related correspondence, circa 1969 (Box 141)
  - Donation receipts, 2001-2002 (Box 141)
  - Writings, 1944, undated (Box 141)
  - Contract agreements and related correspondence, 1964-1966 (Box 141)
  - Family and business files, 1956, circa 2002 (Box 141)
  - Writings, 1982-1998; (43 folders) (Box 142)
    Material are complete and partial, scripts and screenplays. Titles included are Mad Dogs and Englishmen, These are the Jokes, Many Happy Returnes, Has Anybody Seen my Warhol?, Livingston and Evans I Presume, Tony Bennett and the Indians, Here Come the British, You Should Have Been There, Don and Ello, The Funiest WASP, Storm Warning Redux, and others.
  - Notes, correspondence, and ephemera, circa 1990s 2000s; (6 folders) (Box 143)
  - Oklahoma! article, undated (Box 143)
  - Correspondence and business files, circa 1980s-2000s (Box 143)
  - Correspondence, 1960s-1970s; (2 folders) (Box 143)
  - Contract correspondence, 1960s (Box 143)
  - Notebook, undated (Box 143)
  - Writings and correspondence, 2000s (Box 143)
  - Reference materials--The Songs of Irving Berlin, undated (Box 143)
  - Frishberg interview, circa 2000s (Box 143)
    Materials included are writings, notes, and newspaper clippings.
  - Writings and sheet music, Undated (Box 143)
  - Publishing correspondence, circa 1960s-1980s (Box 143)
  - An Academy Salute to Livingston and Evans, 1996-2000 (Box 143)
    Materials included are a brochure, and fax correspondence.
  - Newspaper clippings, circa 1966 (Box 143)
  - Notes and writings, circa 1990s; (11 folders) (Box 144)
    Materials include the scripts The Four Musketeers Out of Town, Has Anybody Seen My Warhol?, Mad Dogs and Englishmen, and other writings.
  - Ephemera, circa 1970s-1990s (Box 144)
  - Research materials, undated (Box 144)
  - Writings, 1951-1961 (Box 145)
    Writings include scripts, and notes by Max Wilk and writings by others. Script titles included are The Kowboys, Mad Money, My Six Convicts, Versailles, All About Love, A Million Laughs, The Belter and the Bat Girl, The Bride Wore a Muzzle and others by Max Wilk.
  - Hotel and travel receipts, 1958- (Box 145)
    Reciepts from the Pennsylvania Railroad, Hotel Taft, and The Warwick.
  - Posters, circa 1950s-1980s (Box 146 (Oversize))
  - Posters, undated (Box 147)
  - Audiovisual materials
    - Audiotape reels, circa 1950s-1960s
      - Side 1 - Friday April 22, Side 2 Saturday - April 23, April 22-23; 1 (Box 148, Item barcode 39002109978685)
      - Mike, Max, WJSG, undated; 1 (Box 148, Item barcode 39002109978693)
      - Tape #2, Jay Williams and me, WQXR, 1959-1960 February; 1 (Box 148, Item barcode 39002109978701)
      - Maxwell's Demon, Tape 6, 1958 October 4; 1 (Box 148, Item barcode 39002109978719)
      - "The Cannon and the Nightingale", musical score, undated; 1 (Box 148, Item barcode 39002109978727)
      - Jazz-1-BIX, undated; 1 (Box 148, Item barcode 39002109978735)
      - Show albums 78, 1968 March; 1 (Box 148, Item barcode 39002109978743)
      - Talk sessions, Moonshot, Ridgefield, Wilk and Gordon, 1964 May; 1 (Box 148, Item barcode 39002109978750)
      - Demon #7, Alex King on [Jack] Paar show, 1959 February 6; 1 (Box 148, Item barcode 39002109978768)
      - Tape #2, undated; 1 (Box 148, Item barcode 39002109978776)
    - Video tapes
      - Reel video tape
        - Chanting and Narration, circa 1980s; 1 (Box 148, Item barcode 39002109978784)
        - Queen Victoria and the Indians, 1984 September 21; 1 (Box 148, Item barcode 39002109978800)
        - Artscape Barbara Wilk, October 25; 1 (Box 148, Item barcode 39002109978792)
        - Mine, 1985 May 28; 1 (Box 148, Item barcode 39002109978818)
      - Videocassettes
        - Prairie Dog Sees, English and Navajo Version, undated; 1; 00:06:48 (Box 149, Item barcode 39002109976333)
          Box 149 (audiovisual material): Restricted fragile. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
        - "Speaking of Art", CPTV, 1979 March 29; 1; 00:24:36; Video clipping can be seen in the recording. (Box 149, Item barcode 39002109976341)
        - Queen Victoria and the Indians, 1984; 1; 00:11:30 (Box 149, Item barcode 39002109976358)
        - MAMA, 1976 July 27; 1; 00:30:23 (Box 149, Item barcode 39002109976366)
        - When TV was Young, 1977 April 19; 1; 00:44:09 (Box 149, Item barcode 39002109976374)
        - 60 Minutes, "Cancer", Burton, undated; 1; 00:18:34 (Box 149, Item barcode 39002109976382)
        - When TV was Young, Reel I, 1977 April 19; 1; 01:00:14 (Box 149, Item barcode 39002109976390)
          Host, Charles Kuralt, takes a look at TV in the 1950s.
        - Untitled, undated; 1; 00:54:18; There is a visible rewind recorded near the end of the tape. (Box 149, Item barcode 39002109976408)
          This videocassette contains an episode of "60 Minutes" that ran on Veterans Day.
        - 1st day readings, rehearsals, shows, 1995 January 22-30; 1; 01:28:59; Video levels vary throughout the program. (Box 149, Item barcode 39002109976416)
        - Letter from an Apache, undated; 1; 00:12:04 (Box 149, Item barcode 39002109976424)
    - Film reels
      - The Shorts Collection, Letter from an Apache, undated; 1 (Box 151)
      - Mine!, undated; 1 (Box 151)
      - Field report, Wilk and Jacoby, undated; 1 (Box 151)
      - Queen Victoria and the Indians, undated; 1 (Box 151)
      - Field report, undated; 1 (Box 151)